goodhoodstore.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy | Goodhood

Goodhood is committed to respecting your privacy and complying with applicable laws and regulations to ensure that the personal information you share with us is kept securely and processed fairly and lawfully. For complete transparency, this Privacy Policy is available on our homepage and at every point where personal information may be requested.

## OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

To protect your personal information online, we use SLL encryption on all data to and from our website. You can check the security validity by clicking the padlock icon that appears in the URL line of your browser.

### What information we collect about you, why do we collect it, and what do we do with it?

When you place an order on our website www.goodhoodstore.com, we collect the following information in order to fulfil your order and contact you should a query arise.

  * your name, 
  * your address,
  * your email address, and
  * your phone number.

When subscribing to our newsletter, we collect the following information in order to send you the products and features we believe may be most relevant 

  * your email address,
  * your gender, and
  * your interests.

### The information we don’t collect 

We never collect credit/debit card information as we use a third party payment processor to handle this information securely. None of your credit/debit card information is stored anywhere on our website.

### How will the information you provide be used?

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with any outside third parties except to the extent necessary to fulfil that order.

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order, or purchasing a gift card, only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside third parties except to the extent necessary to fulfil that order.

You can sign up to receive updates on our latest products and features via email on our website. The information relating to your interests (menswear, womenswear, or homeware) that you provide helps us tailor our messaging. You can always unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time[ here.](https://goodhoodstore.com/mailinglist/unsubscribe)

### Who will my information be shared with? 

As an independent retailer, we do not, and will not, sell any of your personal data to any third party including your name, address, email address, or credit card information.

### How you can access or correct your information 

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You can update your details at any time in the member’s section of our website.

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy, please contact us at webstore@goodhood.co.uk. For security, and to protect your privacy, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## COOKIES

Our website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help provide you with the best experience we can. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile when you browse a website. They provide aggregated but anonymised information and analytics about our customers, but without identifying you. There are 4 types of cookies we may use: 

  * Website functionality cookies which allow you to navigate the website and use our features, such as “Add to Bag” and “Wishlist”.
  * Website analytics cookies which allow us to measure and analyse how our customers use the website, to improve both its functionality and your shopping experience.
  * Customer preference cookies which will remember your preferences (such as your location and local currency) when browsing or shopping on our website, so we can make your shopping experience as seamless as possible and more personal to you.
  * Targeting or advertising cookies which are used to deliver adverts that are relevant to you. They also limit the number of times that you see an advert and help us measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

By using our website, you agree to us placing cookies on your device and accessing them when you visit our website in the future. You can delete any cookies already on your computer within your device’s browser. Please note that by deleting or disabling future cookies, your user experience may be affected and you might not be able to take advantage of certain functions of our website that are designed to give you the best user experience.

You can find out more information about cookies on the ICO website [here.](https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/cookies/)

### OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

We never collect or maintain information on our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13. By placing an order or submitting your details to us, you are confirming that you are over the age of 13. 

### CONTACT US 

If you have any questions or feedback regarding this statement, you can contact us at webstore@goodhood.co.uk.

For more information, please visit the ICO website[ here. ](https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/)

### FUTURE UPDATES

We may change this policy from time to time to ensure it is up to date with current European data protection laws. If there are significant changes to the way we process your data, we’ll notify you via our website, and if you’re subscribed to our mailing list, via email too.

This page was updated on 21st May 2018.
